<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TOEFL Learning App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity_hasil_reading">ActivityHasilReading</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity_hasil_listening">ActivityHasilListening</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity_cek_jawaban_reading">ActivityCekJawabanReading</string>
    <string name="SoalLIsteningB1">Lithuania is very</string>
    <string name="SoalLIsteningB2">in the winter. The snow falls from the beginning of November to the beginnging
     of april. The good thing about snow is that you have white atmosphere everywhere after miserable autum.
     When people walk in snow, they are</string>
    <string name="SoalListeningB3">Belgium in winter is realy miserable.its raining all the time. People look depresed since they can just looka at
    </string>
    <string name="SoalListeningB4">all the time when they are walking outside. The temperature almost reached minus 26 in Lithuania in winter time.
    it was really freezing so that people</string>
    <string name="SoalListeningB5">of their house. When its so cold, it takes a lot of money to heat the house. Aiste father
    combined three heating parts with two different kinds of wood and also natural gas from central heating system. it was really</string>
    <string name="SoalListeningB6">and expensive heating system.</string>
    <string name="MaterialGrammar">Grammar explanation : Adjectives
\n\nSome adjectives go with certain prepositions. There are no grammatical rules for which preposition is used with which adjective, so it\'s a good idea to try to learn them together. To help you do this, write new vocabulary in your notebook in a sentence or phrase.
\nHowever, there are some patterns that can help you. Let\'s look at them first. Remember that a preposition is followed by a noun or a gerund (-ing form).
\n\n
With at
\n
We use at with adjectives like good/bad/amazing/brilliant/terrible, etc. to talk about skills and abilities. Example:
\n
    1. He\'s really good at English.\n
    2. She\'s amazing at the piano.\n
    3. They\'re terrible at organising anything.\n
    4. I\'m not very good at drawing.\n
\n\n
With about
\n
We often use about with adjectives of feelings like angry/excited/happy/nervous/sad/stressed/worried, etc. to explain what is causing that feeling.
\n
    1. I\'m angry about the decision.\n
    2. He\'s nervous about the presentation.\n
    3. She\'s excited about the new job.\n
    4. They were worried about the exam.\n
\n\n
With of
\n
However, sometimes we use of with feelings.
\n
    1. She was afraid of telling her mum.\n
    2. I\'m frightened of having an accident.\n
    3. He\'s scared of flying.\n
    4. You should be proud of your progress.\n
\n\n
With to
\n
We can use to to show the connection between people or things.\n
    1. He\'s married to the director.\n
    2. I\'m addicted to my phone.\n
    3. I\'m allergic to nuts.\n
    4. It\'s similar to the old one.\n
\n
We can also use to to talk about someone\'s behaviour towards someone else.\n
    5. They were really friendly to me.\n
    6. Was he nice to you?\n
    7. He is always polite to everyone.\n
    8. She was very rude to the waitress.\n
\n\n
Here are some other useful adjectives with prepositions.\n
\n
With for\n
    1. Exercise is good for you.\n
    2. Stress is bad for you.\n
    3. The town is famous for its cheese.\n
    4. I\'m responsible for the financial side of the business.\n
\n
With in
\n
    1. She\'s interested in the project.\n
    2. They want someone who\'s experienced in design.\n
    3. I didn\'t want to get involved in the argument.\n
\n
\n
    </string>
</resources>
